<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blog on Eric Lee</title>
    <link>https://ericchanlee.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blog on Eric Lee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Eric Lee 2022</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 10:58:55 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ericchanlee.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Discover Caltech: Lecture on Information Theory</title>
      <link>https://ericchanlee.com/blog/discotech_information_theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 10:58:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ericchanlee.com/blog/discotech_information_theory/</guid>
      <description>Context DiscoTech (Discover Caltech) was a 2 day event, where I had the chance to visit Caltech. There, I attended a mock lecture on information theory by Dr. Michelle Effros. I found it interesting enough for me to share here!
Information Theory Basic Ideas of Information Theory Focuses on 2 questions:
 How to represent information How to transfer information  Need to predict unpredictable events to do so
Predicting Unpredictable Events Imagine you want be a psychic</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No, NFTs aren&#39;t good for Art either</title>
      <link>https://ericchanlee.com/blog/nft_bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 19:59:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ericchanlee.com/blog/nft_bad/</guid>
      <description>A Background Let&amp;rsquo;s get one thing clear; while as a programmer I find the concept of the blockchain interesting, NFTs are a stain in the environment and our culture of cyclic exploitation.
Although I could discuss thoroughly on my dislike of NFTs, this is not a post on:
 The negative environmental impacts of NFTs The regulation of cryptocurrencies The benefits or harms of the blockchain Proof of Work vs Proof of Stake  Instead, this is a discussion on:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Veganism: A Philosophical Argument</title>
      <link>https://ericchanlee.com/blog/veganism_dividing_line/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 19:59:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ericchanlee.com/blog/veganism_dividing_line/</guid>
      <description>The Beginning This will be updated once in a while whenever I decide to have a philosophical crisis. Over the course of the past year, the topic of veganism has been of greater interest to me, and I wanted to organize my own thoughts on the subject.
Predicate assumptions of my current beliefs
 I have strong beliefs on existentialism, and a positive opinion on utilitarianism All of my positions will be based on the importance of philosophical consistency I don&amp;rsquo;t feel any moral disgust over the consumption of meat I&amp;rsquo;m very much stuck in performative activism in terms of environmental regulations Environmental concerns for humans are the primary reason I&amp;rsquo;m considering this, not animals I&amp;rsquo;m taking it as a given that veganism is good for the environment  I&amp;rsquo;ll be going over several points for/against veganism and trying to justify my positions on each.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>